Ally, can we get a recap?
埃莉 能再說一次嗎?
You remember the Kowolskis? They've owned this shop for 30 years
還記得科洛斯基家族嗎? 他們那店已經開了30年了
and they are attempting to set a record by making Buffalo's largest cookie.
他們想打破水牛鎮最大的曲奇的紀錄
- and you have to wear this. - A hairnet?
- 你一定要戴上這東西 - 這發罩?
H.ealth Department.
為了公共衛生
You are kidding.
不要說笑了
If you're around the cookie, you have to have it on.
你想要接近那曲奇你就得遵守規矩
I just did the hair.
我才做了這髮型
The hair is perfect.
多好看
All right, give it to me.
好了好了 給我吧
God... why do you hate me?
上帝 你就這麼恨我嗎?
We're rolling. And speed.
開始... 說話
For three decades, the Kowolski Bakery
三十年以來 科洛斯基自助餐廳
has been a mainstay in downtown Buffalo,
一直都是水牛鎮中心的神話
known for their sinfully sweet, cream-filled Polski pierogies
他們以香甜美味的波蘭式曲奇聞名
and the occasional sugar - induced coma that follows.
他們的餅令人再三回味
Today, in honor of their 30th anniversary,
今天 在他們的三十年店慶典禮上
they've invited us to ride along as they go for the record
他們邀請我們一同見證 他們將打破
on Buffalo's biggest cookie.
水牛鎮最大的曲奇的紀錄
Vol. Do you need a tissue or something?
沃爾 要紙巾嗎?
Can we get Vol a tissue? Or a spoon?
你要張紙巾嗎? 還是要個勺子?
Good thing we're wearing these.
我也戴上了這個
I wouldn't want any stray hairs to fall into the booger.
以免我的頭髮掉在這破玩意上
- We doing this again? - No. We can cut to B roll.
- 這段會放出去嗎? - 不 我們會剪掉它
Moving on!
我們繼續
Tell me, Mama, why make Buffalo's biggest cookie?
老媽媽 告訴我 為什麼你要做最大的曲奇餅?
Well, man from Health Department say
這樣的 衛生局的人來說 說
he find rat pellet in our pastry.
他們在我的奶油裡發現死老鼠
But I say no, is big chocolate sprinkle.
我說 那不是 那是一大塊巧克力
But he shut store down.
但他還是封了鋪
So we clean up,
那我們就搞乾淨
make big cookie for to bring customers back.
做一個大的曲奇餅 把客人攬回來
Well, I admire your candor.
嗯 你還真坦白
Let's try that again, shall we?
我們要重新來一遍嗎?
Tell me, Mama, why make Buffalo's biggest cookie?
老媽媽 告訴我 為什麼要做水牛鎮最大的曲奇
So the children of the neighborhood will be happy.
這個大麯奇餅一定會令鄰居的小孩很開心
It must be wonderful seeing the smiles on their little faces.
對 能看到他們的小臉上掛著微笑是多麼美好
I work in back. I see no smiles.
我在廚房做事 看不到那些微笑
The previous record was 8 feet 7 inches, baked by Gladys Pelsnick.
現在的紀錄是2.60米直徑 是克拉麗斯所創造的
If this cookie beats that, it will prove
如果這塊曲奇能比克拉麗斯的大 那就能證明
the Kowolskis have much more free time.
科洛斯基家族更加閑著無聊
And the cookie is... 10 feet, 4 inches!
這曲奇是... 3.14米!
We have a new record!
新紀錄誕生了!
Cue the cheesy inspirational music!
來段破紀錄的音樂!
But what are we really looking at here?
但是在這裡你所發現的
Is it just a big cookie?
只是一個大麯奇嗎?
Or does this cookie represent the pride of Buffalo?
還是一個水牛鎮的驕傲的象徵?
Its hard - working citizens the key ingredient
以市民的勤勞和忘我工作作為主材料
with a few nuts thrown in.
加上兩塊"傻瓜"
And finally, the love of our families,
最後 再加上家庭的愛
which provides the warm center,
溫暖的親情
making our beloved Buffalo the sweetest place to live.
令我們所愛的水牛鎮成為一個宜人居住的地方
And that's the way the cookie crumbles.
曲奇是這樣製成的
I'm Bruce Nolan, Eyewitness News.
這裡是布魯斯·諾蘭 直擊新聞
And cut.
卡...
So what do you think?
覺得怎樣?
It's really good.
我覺得很好
It sucks. It's a story about a cookie.
討厭極了 一個曲奇的故事
The Pillsbury Doughboy would be riveted.
我看起來像個傻子
It made me laugh. Nothing wrong with making people laugh.
親愛的 這很有趣 我都忍不住笑了 讓人笑不好嗎?
I'll never be an anchorman.
但這樣我永遠不能成為電視臺的主持
The job's there, but I can't reach it.
伸手可觸 但我就是得不到
Every time they make me do this kind of stuff I have to act like a goof.
因為我老是在幹這種事情 我要扮得像個傻瓜一樣
I have no credibility. Not good.
人們覺得我不可靠 這一點也不好... 不好
- Now you just sound silly. - Forget it.
- 知道嗎? 你說這話才像個傻瓜 - 算了
It's not important. Let's watch it one more time.
這不重要 對嗎? 這不重要 我們再看一遍
- No. - Once more? Please?
- 噢 不 - 就一次 求你
No! You promised to help me with this photo album.
不要 布魯斯 你答應過我會幫我整理照片的!
Now get your gooy butt over here.
把你那傻瓜的屁股擺這裡來
Looking.
不要"嗯"
Ok
好
Just go through this stack and pick your favorites.
看看這一疊 把你最喜歡的挑出來
Come on. This is fun, right?
看這有趣 不是嗎?
Isn't this fun? This is nice.
真有趣 這張不錯
Evan's going to get that anchor job.
如果我能夠成為主持人
- Bruce! - He's the favorite.
- 布魯斯! - 這才是我最喜歡的
You know what? Just forget it. This is just our life.
算了 算了 這就是我們的生活
We can always just have some kid do it for us.
或許生個小孩來整理吧
Hold the phone.
噢 別掛線
I like this one. Our weekend at the lake.
我喜歡這張 我們在湖邊的週末
That's supposed to be in our private stash.
這是我的私人珍藏
- You look perky. Must have been cold. - Give it to me.
- 沒有穿衣服啊 一定很冷吧 - 還給我
I think I'll put this on my computer.
我要把它掃描進電腦裡當壁紙
- Give it to me. Come on. - No!
- 好了 還給我! - 不不不
Fine. Do with it what you will.
好了 你想幹什麼隨便
I don't care.
我不理了
- I will do with it what I will. - Jesus.
- 我會的 - 上帝啊
I might even send this in to Playboy.
我會把它送到"花花公子"去
- Their layouts can be quite tasteful. - Give that to me right now!
- 聽說他們也刊登讀者來照 - 馬上還給我
- Rough stuff. - I'm going to hurt you.
- 專業打手! - 抓住我!
Sweetie? Time to get up.
親愛的 要起床了
Good dream. No.
不要 我還在做夢
The Buffalo Sabres lost again last night to the Toronto Maple Leafs.
水牛鎮剃刀隊昨晚又輸一場 他們對陣多倫多楓葉隊
Of course they did. They're my team.
是我支持的球隊 當然輸了
That's the way the cookie crumbles.
曲奇是這樣製成的
There might be something to this cookie line.
我想這句曲奇對白不錯
The greatest anchors have a signature sign - off. Like Walter Cronkite.
每個台柱都有自己的口頭禪 像沃爾特·克朗凱特
And that's the way it was.
鋼鐵是這樣煉成的
That's the way the cookie crumbles.
曲奇是這樣煉成的
That's the way I like it
這個就是 啊哈 我喜歡這樣
Oh, no.
噢 慘了
- Grace, the dog! - I'm in the shower!
- 格雷斯 你的狗! - 我在洗澡!
No, Sam. Bad dog.
壞狗狗!
Inside, bad. Outside, good.
裡面不行 外面行
You're done now. Great.
已經拉完了? 好極了
B-E-A-utiful.
潑... 伊... 傲... 漂亮
Come on. Let's go back in and have a shit.
來 我們進去拉屎
- What is the dillio? - We are having a blood drive.
- 那是在幹什麼? - 在搞獻血活動
- Needles. Yuck. - They need my blood.
- 拿針紮人 - 他們需要我的血
I have a very rare blood type. I'm AB positive.
我的是小血型 AB+型
Really? I'm IB positive.
是嗎? 我的是IB+型
I B positive they ain't touching me with no needle. It's just so...
他們不敢拿針動我 這真是... 有意義
- Helpful and life - saving? - No. It's blood.
- 可以救人一命 - 不 這些是血
Blood is supposed to stay inside the body, where it's meant to be.
血是應該在體內流動的 這才能叫血
Besides, they stockpile this stuff in a warehouse, it's all on ice,
但這些人 他們把血裝起來再放到什麼室裡倒掉
and they say there's a shortage.
然後他們就說缺血
Where did you hear that?
不是這樣的 你哪裡聽回來的?
From a friend of a friend
從一個政府高官的姨媽的弟弟的侄女
of a girl whose sister is going out with someone in the government.
的同學的同事的女友的朋友那裡聽回來的
For your protection, I cannot discuss it.
但我今天不能跟你討論這問題了
Now get out, before they see us together.
出去吧 趁他們還沒見到我們在一起
Here. You need these more than I do.
等等 你比我更需要這個
What is "these"?
這個是什麼?
Prayer beads. The kids made them for me.
護身符 一個小孩做給我的
- They will keep you safe. - I hope they're powerful.
- 能保你平安 - 最好它真能帶來奇跡
I'm going to need a friggin' miracle to get to work on time.
否則我趕不及上班了
This isn't happening. Not now. Not during sweeps week.
不是吧 別這樣對我 別在這種時候 別在這種時候這樣對我!
Oh, God.
上帝
Yup, meeting started without me.
好了 開會了 我趕不上了
This is my luck.
這就是我的命!
Come on.
快! 快! 快!
Jesus.
上帝啊
Get out of there!
出來!
"Are you blind? " No, but I'm late.
你是"瞎子"嗎? 不 但我要遲到了
Is your child in dire jeopardy?
你的孩子正面臨死亡的威迫嗎?
Find out tonight after the game.
今晚比賽後告你
Promos are approved.
Ok 通過了
Jack? Shouldn't we be focusing on Pete's retirement?
傑克 我們不是應該關注多點皮特的退休嗎?
- This is his last week. - Any word on the anchor position?
- 這星期以後他就不做了 - 對 他的職位會空出來
Evan, when I know something, you'll know something.
埃文 我想到的事 你總能想到
Sorry I'm late.
對不起 我來遲了
Traffic was...
大塞車
Did you already play the spots?
你們看過我的報導了嗎?
Nice story, but we're going with Evan's piece.
你的故事挺有趣 布魯斯 但我們還是挑了埃文的
The sex scandal in the mayor's office for sweeps.
市長內閣的性醜聞事件
Yeah. Sweeps.
噢 對 醜聞
And that's the way the cookie crumbles.
曲奇是這樣製成的
I'm just messing with you, Bruce.
我印象深刻 布魯斯
See, you just gotta remember that the newsroom
你要記住 新聞就像
is like a big cookie.
一大塊 曲奇
Do you like jazz, Evan? Let me play something for you.
埃文你喜歡爵士樂嗎? 讓我為你奏一曲
- I can hold that note all day. - Knock it off, guys.
- 我可以給你看一整天 - 夥計們 冷靜點
We'll keep your story in reserve.
布魯斯 你的報導我會留著後備
Can we get back to the board so we'll have something to put on the air today?
現在看著白板 看看今天應該播放什麼
Great choice, Jack. The Cadillac of bolognas.
有眼光 傑克! 這些是最上等的
Jack, can I talk to you?
傑克 能談幾句嗎?
- Sure. What do you need? - Sweeps.
- 當然 布魯斯 說吧 - 是報導
Jack, hear me out. I'm starting to get desperate.
傑克 你一定要幫幫我
I'm pushing 40 and what have I got to show?
我已經40了 我以後怎麼過?
I've hit a kind of ceiling.
我在這裡已經變了一個傻瓜
There's an anti - Bruce barrier I can't get past.
我的前途有一個"反 布魯斯"的牌子 不讓我通過
And Evan is loving it.
但埃文呢 他受人崇拜
He gets the stories, he gets on sweeps... I should be more like Evan.
他有他的故事 有他的素材 我想我也應該有這樣的待遇
Don't be like Evan. Evan's an asshole.
你想像埃文一樣? 埃文是個混蛋
- I can be an asshole. - No, Bruce. You can't.
- 我也可以做個混蛋 - 不 布魯斯 你不能
- You going to pick that up? - Yeah. I'm sorry.
- 還不給我撿起來? - 對不起
This anchor thing opening up has got me nuts.
我太想成為台柱了
- Hi, Susan. - Hi, Jack.
- 嗨 蘇珊 - 嗨 傑克
You're a good reporter. You make people laugh.
布魯斯 你是個好記者 你能讓觀眾笑
All right. I'll tell you what.
好了 這樣吧今天是
Today is the 156th anniversary of the Maid Of The Mist.
"霧之少女"號的156歲紀念
I want you in Niagara Falls in an hour.
我要你到瀑布裡呆一個小時 "霧之少女"號製造周年紀念?
The Maid Of The Mist is always live.
那就是直播了?
- Evan always does the live feeds. - Now you and Evan get the live feeds.
- 但我不是幹直播的人 - 那你現在就是幹直播的人
I'm going live? During sweeps?
我要直播新聞?
Watch your step. I've seen your out takes.
但小心點布魯斯 這次可不能剪片的
Jack, you will not regret this.
傑克 你一定不會後悔的
And I won't forget you when I go national.
我出名後一定不會忘記你的
Can you...?
能不能?
Thanks, pal.
謝謝
Can I have your wish now? I'll put it in the wish jar.
你的願望星好了嗎? 放到這瓶裡 謝謝
Put your wish in.
把願望放到瓶子裡
- Me, too. - Put your wish in.
- 我也有 - 放到這瓶裡
That looks like a big wish.
看 這一定是個很大的願望
No, Martin, don't eat that.
噢 別! 別! 馬克不要吃
Don't put that in your mouth. That's paste, honey.
這是漿糊 不要放到嘴裡去
- That must have tasted awful. - Mommy!
- 一定是很難吃的 - 媽咪
Did you have a good time with Aunt Gracie today?
今天有沒有聽 格雷斯阿姨的話?
- See how nice this is? Baby on the hip. - It's amazing. You've become Mom.
- 看著多棒 抱著一個寶寶 - 噢 太棒了
The transformation is complete.
你已經是"媽媽"了 成功轉型了
I'll get it.
我來聽
- Small Wonders Day Care. - Grace?
- 小奇觀托兒所 - 格雷斯?
It's Debbie, the sister whose life you're not wasting.
不 我是黛比 被你毀掉幸福的人的姐姐
- OK. - Bye, Debbie!
- 好了 我來聽 - 你好 黛比!
Hi. Sorry.
你好!
Debbie forgot to take her meds today. Where are you?
不要怪黛比 你在哪?
A little place called the winner's circle.
一個旅遊勝地
I'm at the falls, doing a live report.
我在瀑布裡 要做現場直播
Live? That's great!
做現場直播? 那太好了!
Yeah! It's happening, hon. I got sweeps and I'm live.
對! 就是這樣 親愛的 像埃文一樣有機會
They're seeing if I can think on my feet.
知道這是什麼意思嗎? 我不用再靠人了
Like I might have to do in a live anchor situation.
我快要成為主持人了
Oh, my gosh.
我的天
Yeah! Jack practically came out and told me.
對!! 實際上 傑克 要讓我上位
Practically?
實際上?
He didn't spell it out. Legally, he can't.
對 他沒有說出來 因為在程式上他不能說
This is what happened to Susan Ortega
但現在就像蘇珊·奧爾特加成為真正主持人前
before they bumped her up to the desk.
所經歷的一樣
It's good.
太好了 太好了
Well, honey, I just don't want you to get too ahead of yourself.
太好了 但親愛的 現在還不應該太高興
- Bruce. - I got to go!
- 布魯斯 - 我要開始了
- They're calling me in. - OK, honey. Good luck. I love you.
- 他們在叫我了 - 好的 親愛的 好運 我愛你!
Let's do it.
來吧
- They want you close to the falls. - I'm going to get soaked.
- 他們向你接近瀑布 - 真的? 那不就要濕了
That's the point. They want you to put this on.
正是這樣 他們要你戴上這個
Part of the condition of us getting the exclusive.
保持你一向的形象
You know what? Nothing can bother me today. Nothing.
知道嗎? 今天我什麼都不介意
Now remember, it's their 156th - year anniversary.
好了記住 是156歲
149 capacity. They cater to tourists, honeymooners...
有149個旅客 他們有的來度假 有的來度蜜月
And people who are insanely thirsty. I get it.
還有想來喝水的人 明白了
You're going to interview Irene Dansfield.
還有你要採訪愛琳
Irene, a pleasure to meet you. You look beautiful.
愛琳! 很高興見到你 真的 你看上去好漂亮
Irene's mother rode on the maiden voyage.
愛琳的母親參加過這船的處女行
- Rub that in my face! - 90 seconds!
- 哇! 那可真令人吃驚 - 90秒? 天啊
Holy hell.
90秒? 呼...
Because of the fast response,
由於快速行動 所有有毒物質
the chemicals were cleaned up without incident. Susan?
在事故發生前已經撤走 蘇珊
Bruce Nolan is at Niagara Falls.
布魯斯·諾蘭 現在正在尼加拉瓜大瀑布前
But before we go live to Bruce, we have an announcement.
但在布魯斯的直播前 我們有一則重要新聞
As everyone knows, after 33 years,
大家都知道 我們敬愛的皮特
our beloved Pete Fineman is retiring.
在工作33年後宣佈退休
Pete's shoes are virtually impossible to fill, but the show must go on.
皮特已經不會再工作了 但他的節目還會繼續下去
And we could think of no one better than our very own Evan Baxter.
沒人能代替他的地位 除了埃文·巴克斯特
Oh, boy!
噢 老天
- Congratulations. - I'm thrilled and honored.
- 恭喜你 埃文 - 謝謝
As you said, no one can replace Pete, but I will do my best.
像你所說的 沒人能代替偉大的皮特 但我會盡力的
I am so proud to be a part of our local community of Buffalo.
我必須說 能成為水牛鎮的市民很榮幸
I think, in a lot of ways, a great city is like a great recipe, really.
而我相信 一個偉大的城市就像一張偉大的菜譜
You take hard - working citizens, add some care - givers,
放點勤勞 加點團結
maybe a few nuts!
或許加幾片"傻瓜"
All sprinkled with the love and support of our good families.
所有這些再加上來自家庭的愛與鼓勵
Ultimately, that makes one sweet place to live.
就炒成一道 甜蜜之家
- That was amazing. - I wish I'd written something.
- 說的很好 - 沒什麼 只是有感而發
And now let's go live to that wacky
現在讓我們回到報導現場
Bruce Nolan at Niagara Falls.
怪人布魯斯·諾蘭 在尼加拉瓜大瀑布報導
Hey, wacky Bruce!
嘿 怪人 布魯斯
- Talk, Bruce. Hello. - Talk, honey.
- 布魯斯? 說話啊 布魯斯 喂? - 說話啊 親愛的
- What's going on? - A Walt Disney.
- 怎麼回事? - 那個怪人
- It's frozen solid. - Check the feed.
- 他定格了 可能是沒聲音 - 檢查信號
We may be having technical difficulty.
我們遇到一點技術問題
- The feed's good, Jack. - Come on.
- 信號沒問題 傑克 - 說話啊 布魯斯!
- Talk, Bruce, damn it. - Get ready to pull the plug.
- 該死的! - 做好最壞打算
Come on, baby. Say something!
親愛的 說話啊 說話啊
Bruce, talk.
布魯斯 說話!
- Hi, Susan. - Thank you, God.
- 嗨 蘇珊! - 謝天謝地
Bruce Nolan here,
這裡是布魯斯·諾蘭
aboard the Maid Of The Mist in fabulous Niagara Falls, New York.
我在"霧之少女"號上 身後是紐約美麗的尼加拉瓜大瀑布
First, let me just add another congratulations to Evan Backstabber.
首先 讓我恭喜 埃文·巴克斯特
Pardon me, Bastard... Baxter.
應該是埃文大混蛋
It is good to see what someone with real talent can do
讓我們看看他有沒有能耐
when great opportunities are given to them instead of me.
應付本來應該給我的好機會
Anyway, I'm here with Katharine Hepburn's mom.
無論如何 我身邊的是凱薩琳的母親
Why did you throw the Heart of the Ocean jewel over the railing of the Titanic?
告訴我 為什麼你要把海洋之心帶上泰坦尼克號?
Did you feel bad letting Leo DiCaprio drown
你把利奧納多留在冰水裡
while you were safe floating on the door?
而自己就趴在大門上是不是很過癮?
Could you have taken turns?
你不想換他上去?
Or were you too afraid to freeze your big fat ass off?
還是你的大胖屁股被凍住了?
I guess that's how life is.
這就是命
Some people are drenched, freezing on a stupid boat with a stupid hat,
有些人在冷得要命的船上等死 還要戴著這種帽子
while others are in a news studio, sucking up the glory.
而另外一些人就舒舒服服 得呆在錄影廠裡領功
Oh, well. No big deal.
哦 不錯哦 夥計
The owner of the Maid Of The Mist. Let's have a talk with him.
那是"霧之少女"號的主人 我們跟他談一談
Come on in here, Bill. No, let's have a talk.
來這邊 比爾 別別別 我們來談談
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼?
You've been running the Maid Of The Mist for 23 years.
你已經擁有"霧之少女"號23年了 你說
Why do you think I didn't get anchor?
為什麼我不能成為主持人呢?
- I don't want any problems. - Is it my hair?
- 我不知道怎麼回事 - 因為我的髮型不好看嗎?
Are my teeth not white enough? Or, like the great falls,
還是我的牙不夠白? 還是我的命就像
is the bedrock of my life eroding beneath me?
大瀑布下的石頭
Eroding!
你一生都得被我踩
你一生都得被我踩!
- Cut the feed. Go to black. - I'm on it.
取消直播
I'm Bruce Nolan, for Eyewitness News. Back to you, fuckers!
這裡是布魯斯·諾蘭直擊新聞 交給你們 他媽的!
- Oh, boy. - Oh, my God.
我的天
That is perfect.
太棒了!
That is the motivation that I needed!
這才是我需要的激勵
Right there! Thank you!
就這樣! 謝謝
Thank you, WKBW.
謝謝 WKBW!
Wimpy... Kitty Baby Whiners!
軟弱無能的基蒂寶貝悲訴者!
That's what that stands for!
就是代表這個意思
I'll see you on Channel 5.
我要跳去5頻道
Where they do the real news!
他們才是真正報導新聞的
Do I look blind to you?
我看起來很盲目嗎?
Let's go, man. Come on.
我們走吧 快點
What are you doing?
你們在幹什麼?
Come on. Leave the poor guy alone!
不要搞這可憐的人
You OK, man?
你沒事吧?
Yeah, you better keep walking.
你們有種就別走
- What'd you say, ese? - Run, man!
- 什麼? 你說什麼? - 快逃阿!
Run!
快跑
Oh, God!
上帝!
OK, I didn't mean it!
好了好了 我不是認真的
- I was just kidding! - Hey, you forgot your things.
- 開玩笑的 - 嘿 你忘記拿東西了
Say something now!
看你還敢多嘴 還敢再說
B - E - A...
潑... 伊... 傲... 漂
..utiful.
漂亮
That's what I get...
這就是報應
That's what I get for trying to help someone.
我幫人的報應
Don't look at me, Walter.
不要望著我 沃爾特
Oh, no!
噢 不!
That's my payment, I guess.
我想這就是我的報應了
That is my reward.
我應得的
Just? Just get a clue!
人生就是? 就是尋尋覓覓!
Thank God you're all right.
感謝上帝 你沒事
God, yeah. Let's thank God.
上帝... 我們要感謝上帝嗎?
For his blessings are raining down upon me.
感謝他的祝福降臨在我身上.
- Wait! That's not rain! - Bruce, please don't do that.
- 不過 這不是雨嘛? - 別這樣 布魯斯
Everything happens for a reason.
凡事看開點...
That I don't need. That is a clich? That is not helpful.
這種陳詞濫調對我沒用 我不需要
"A bird in the hand is worth two in the bush."
"二鳥在林不如一鳥在手"!
I have no bird! No bush! God has taken my bird and my bush.
我沒有鳥! 也沒有林!
I see. So God is picking on you?
上帝把我的鳥從我的林裡拿走了
No! He's ignoring me completely.
噢... 我明白了... 你是說上帝是故意找你的碴? 是不是?
He's busy giving Evan everything he wants.
他在忙著滿足埃文!
Great, Sam. But you missed your target. I'm over here!
你太棒了 薩姆... 但你搞錯目標了 我在這裡!
Don't get mad at the dog. It's not his fault.
又不是狗的錯 幹嘛沖他發火!
It's God's fault. He gave him the wrong co - ordinates.
對 是上帝的錯 他把一切都搞亂套了
Enough! Will you stop being such a martyr?
夠了 說的好像你被人謀殺了一樣
I am not being a martyr! I'm a victim!
我不是被人謀殺 我是個犧牲品!
God is a mean kid with a magnifying glass, and I'm the ant.
上帝是個壞小孩 他坐在那裡 手上拿著放大鏡
He could fix my life if he wanted,
他只要5分種就能改變我的命運 如果他高興的話
but he'd rather burn off my feelers and watch me squirm.
可他卻放任那個傢伙對我為所欲為!
Sweetheart, I know you're mad.
我知道你很生氣
What Evan did was slimy and wrong.
我完全明白埃文對你做的一切都是錯的
This day could have been so much worse. I'm just glad you're OK.
但我真的很高興你今天能平安無事
OK? News flash! I'm not OK.
平安無事? "新聞簡訊"呢? 我有事!
I'm not OK with a mediocre job!
我討厭我做的那些平庸的事情!
Or a mediocre apartment!
我討厭我住的這間平庸的公寓!
I'm not OK with a mediocre life!
我討厭我過的這種平庸的生活!
Is that what you think we have? A mediocre life?
我們在一起 也是平庸的生活?
Don't make this about you.
別把這件事情扯到你身上
About me? How could I make this about me?
什麼... 怎麼可能扯到我身上?
It's about you. It's always about you.
這是你的事情 永遠都是你的事情
Perfect.
太好了! 太好了!
I'll have the worst day of my life with
今天是我一生中最糟的一天
a side order of guilt, please!
請不要再讓我有罪惡感了 行嗎?
OK, God. You want me to talk to you?
好罷... 上帝 你要和我說話嗎?
Then talk back. Tell me what's going on.
那就回答我 告訴我這是怎麼了
What should I do? Give me a signal.
我該怎麼辦? 給我個信號吧
I need your guidance, Lord. Please, send me a sign.
你指引過什麼人嗎? 給我指示吧!
Oh, what's this joker doing now?
噢 現在又在耍什麼把戲?
OK. All right. I'll try it your way.
好... 好吧... 我就試試你的方式
All right. Lord... I need a miracle.
好的... 主啊... 我需要奇跡
I'm desperate.
我很絕望...
I need your help, Lord.
我需要你的説明 主啊
Please, reach into my life...
求你了... 進入我的生活...
What the...? Where are you?
你在那兒啊?
Got you!
我靠...
Fine!
好了
The gloves are off, pal!
手鏈已經脫掉了!
Come on! Let me see a little wrath!
來吧 譴責我吧!
Smite me, O mighty smiter!
毀滅我吧! 噢... 你不是很厲害的嗎?
You're the one who should be fired!
你才是該被炒魷魚的人!
The only one around here not doing his job is you!
你才是從來不做事的人! 是你!
Answer me!
回答我啊!
Sorry. Don't know you.
不好意思... 我不認識你
Wouldn't call you if I did.
認識你的話... 我就會回電話了
Oh, God!
不要 上帝 不要
Hello, 555-0123.
你好... 555-0123
Oh, no! Sam, this has got to stop!
天啊 不要! 停止吧!
Get it straight. That's the house. This is the bathroom.
好了 我們直說吧 那是房子 這是廁所
House, bathroom. Bathroom, house.
房子... 廁所... 廁所... 房子
What's the point?
真是對狗彈琴...
555-0123...
555轉0123...
Denied that promotion? Is life unfair?
"升職被拒了嗎? " "生活是不是很不公平? "
Is someone less talented than you reaping the benefits?
"比你差的人卻搶走了本該屬於你的一切? "
Is your name Bruce?
"你的名字是布魯斯嗎? "
Then do we have the job for you!
"那麼我們有份工作要給你"
We're located at 77256, 23rd Street.
"我們在第23大街77256號"
So come on down - or we'll just keep beeping you.
"快來吧 不然我們會一直呼你的! "
"Omni Presents."
"全能的現在"
Oh, yeah. The glass is half - full.
... 玻璃半關著
Come on! Look! What is that?
天啊! 看看吧! 那是什麼! 那是什麼!
Thank you again.
天呐... 謝謝... 再次感謝
What the...?
這...
You're looking for room 7.
你要去7號房
- Yeah, I figured. - Want me to even those up for you?
- 是的 我想是 - 你這樣沒事嗎?
- How do I get to room 7? - That'd be on the 7th floor.
- 7號房怎麼走? - 在7樓
- Stairs are over there. - I'll take the elevator.
- 樓梯在那邊 - 好 我坐電梯
- Out of order. - The stairs were my second choice.
- 電梯壞了 - 但其實我也蠻喜歡走樓梯的 它是我的第二選擇
Do you mind giving me a hand with this floor?
你能幫我清潔這一層嗎?
What? That's good.
什麼?... 不錯
Are you serious?
你說真的?
I'm kind of busy. Rain check.
我有點忙 留著我下次做吧
I'll hold you to it.
等你哦
I'm free on the 7th at 7.00.
7點我有空 7點!
The 7th at 7.00 it is.
7點就7點吧
This looks promising.
他很守信用啊
Hello?
有人嗎!
Another hug antic, gnostic waste of my life.
這樣浪費我的時間真有創意
Hello?
有人嗎?
I'm looking for whoever runs this joint!
你是這裡的頭頭嗎?
Be right with you. I'm fixing a light.
就來 我在修燈
Tell me if it's working.
幫我看看修好了沒
Yeah. Seems to be.
是的 好象是修好了
- Kind of bright, though. - Yeah. It is for most people.
- 不過有點刺眼 - 是的 大多數人都是這樣...
Spend their lives in the dark, trying to hide from me.
在黑暗裡度過一生... 想要躲開我
The elevator's broken, huh?
電梯不是壞了嗎?
Yeah, but I'll get around to it.
對 不過... 我會修好的
- You installed a clapper? - No, but catchy jingle, isn't it?
- 你裝了聲控裝置? - 沒有... 不過那首廣告曲很好玩對吧?
Clap on, clap off
"拍手打開... 拍手關閉... "
The clapper
啪啪牌聲控
Just can't get it out of my head.
繞梁三日啊
Well, good luck with that.
那麼祝你好運...
- I'm going to go now. - OK.
- 現在我要走了 - 好吧
But the boss will be right out.
老闆馬上就來了
You must be Bruce. I've been expecting you.
你一定是布魯斯 我一直在等你
This is hilarious.
有意思...
You're the boss, electrician and janitor.
你是老闆 又是電工 還是清潔工?
Must be a killer Christmas party.
這一定是瘋狂聖誕派對?
Don't get drunk, though. One of you might need a ride home.
那別喝醉了哦... 要我送你回去嘛?
You always were funny, Bruce. Just like your father.
你總是很會逗人開心 布魯斯 和你父親一樣
He didn't mind rolling up his sleeves either.
他也不介意卷起袖子幹活
People underestimate the benefit of manual labor. There's freedom in it.
人們常常會低估體力勞動的好處
Some of the happiest people smell to
那些工作一天后回到家裡 滿身汗臭的人們
high heaven at the end of the day.
他們才是世界上最幸福的人
All right, what is this?
這是怎麼回事?
How do you know my father
我自己都不認識我父親 你是怎麼認識的?
and how did you get my number?
還有 你是怎麼知道我的呼機號的?
I know a lot about you, Bruce.
我知道你的事情可多了... 布魯斯
Just about everything there is to know.
不是每件事情都說得出原因的
Everything you've ever said or done or thought about doing.
你說過的每一句話 做過的每一件事 心中轉過的每一個念頭
Right there in that file cabinet.
都在那個檔櫃裡
- Wow! A whole drawer, just for me. - Yeah.
- 喔... 我的整櫃人生嗎? - 對
Mind if I take a look?
我可以看一下嗎?
It's your life.
這是你的生活
This oughta be good.
聽上去不錯...
This last entry was a little disturbing.
最後一筆記錄有點煩人.
"The gloves are off, God."
"手鏈脫掉了 上帝... "
"God has taken my bird and my bush."
"上帝把我的鳥和我的林都搶走了"
"God is a mean kid with a magnifying glass."
"上帝是個拿著放大鏡的壞小孩"
"Smite me, O mighty smiter."
"毀滅我吧 萬能的毀滅者"
I'm not much for blaspheming, but that last one made me laugh.
我不怎麼支持褻瀆神靈 不過最後這條記錄讓我捧腹
Are you spying on me?
你監視我?
Who are you?
你是誰?
I am the One.
我就是那個人
Creator of the heavens and the earth. Alpha and Omega.
我創造了天與地... 以及世間的一切
I see where this is going.
噢... 我明白這是怎麼回事了
Bruce... I am God.
布魯斯 我是上帝!
Bingo! Yahtzee!
猜中了! 對呀!
Is that your final answer? Our survey says, "God! "
這是你的最終答案嗎? 答案是... 上帝!
It was nice to meet you, God.
很高興認識你 上帝
Thanks for the Grand Canyon. Good luck with the Apocalypse.
謝謝你創造了大峽谷 希望你世界末日那天平安無事
And by the way, you suck!
順便說一句... 你太失敗了!
It would have been more impressive
如果你不用這個蹩腳的櫃子當道具
if you hadn't used the cheesy file cabinet illusion.
你的表演會顯得更真實一些
Anybody with a brain stem can tell that drawer
只要是有腦子的人都看得出來
is being fed through the wall from the other side.
這個櫃子是從牆的反面彈出來的
All you have to do is find the crease right around here.
我只需要找到這條縫...
There is a seam here, or a hollow spot.
就在這裡... 只要找到空心的地方
Where?
在哪裡?
Through the dry wall and concrete?
隔著牆和磚的那一面嗎?
OK, that is a good one.
很了不起! 真的很了不起!
- How many fingers am I holding up? - Thou shalt not tempt the Lord.
- 好... 猜我伸出了幾隻手指? - 布魯斯 決不要讓上帝...
- If you can't do it... - Three.
- 猜不出也沒什麼的... - 3!
Two... four... nine.
二... 四... 九.
Six... eight... one.
六... 八... 一.
OK.
好...
How many now?
現在呢?
Seven.
七
- How? - You've been complaining about me.
- 怎麼會... - 你總是對我抱怨個不停 布魯斯
- I'm tired of it. - Don't come near me. Seriously.
- 說實話 我快要受不了了 - 等等 別靠近我 說真的
I don't want to hurt you,
我被逼急了會變成只野獸的 我不想傷害到你
but I will out of instinct.
但這是我的本能
You haven't won a fight since grade 5, and that was against a girl.
你最後一次打架是在五年級 和一個女生...
But she was huge. She'd been held back.
但她很壯... 最後退卻的也是她
And the sun was in your eyes.
你眼中的有的是太陽
Ah, the ego.
而不是妄自菲薄
Anyway, I brought you here to offer you a job.
不管怎麼說 讓你來這裡是有工作要給你做
- A job? What job? - My job.
- 工作... 什麼工作? - 我的工作
You think you can do it better, so here's your chance.
既然你覺得你可以做得更好 我就給你這個機會
When you leave this building, you will be endowed with all my powers.
當你離開這座大樓的時候 你會擁有我所有的神力
Sure. Whatever you say, pal.
沒問題 隨你怎麼說了 兄台
OK. That did not happen. No one needs to hear about it.
好了 什麼都沒發生過 沒有人會知道這個
I'm deleting the program.
除非我在節目中報導
No.
不... 不...
I'm having a breakdown.
這是我的幻覺 我的精神狀況一團糟
Everyday psychotic episode, caused by a tumor, a brain lesion.
這很正常... 心理作用 由腫瘤壓迫大腦產生的幻覺
Come on. Start!
快... 發動!
That was lucky.
碰巧走運而已
Come on. Calm down.
拜託... 冷靜下來
You did not meet God. You do not have his powers.
你不是上帝... 你也沒有神力
If that was God, I'm Clint Eastwood.
如果他是上帝 我就是克林特·伊斯特伍德
Holy hell!
天啊!
Be careful what you wish for, punk.
小心別許錯了願哦... 笨蛋!
Nope!
不! 不!
I am a reasonable, sane human being.
我是個理智的人類!
With a.44 Magnum.
點44左輪...
The most powerful handgun in the...
世界上威力最強的手槍
I'm not Clint Eastwood. I'm Bruce Nolan.
我不是克林特·伊斯特伍德... 我是布魯斯·諾蘭!
I'm Bruce Nolan!
布魯斯·諾蘭... 布魯斯·諾蘭
That was not real.
這不是真的...
- Coffee? - Coffee, yeah.
- 要咖啡嗎? - 好... 咖啡... 好
We have a special on soup today.
我們今天有特色湯點
- No, thank you. - It's tomato. I made it myself.
- 不用 夠了 謝謝... - 是番茄湯 我親手做的哦
OK.
好的
Excuse me, I need a spoo - ...
對不起... 我要只勺... 子
It's OK. I found one.
不需要了 我找到了一隻
Here's your soup.
你的湯來了
Oh, soup, right.
噢... 湯... 好的...
Yeah, right.
好的...
Having fun?
很好玩吧?
Thy, thou...
你...
Come. Take a closer walk with me.
來 我們出去走走
- Let me explain the rules. - Rules?
- 我來解釋一下規則 - 規則?
You left in such a rush, I didn't get a chance to explain.
是啊 你走得太快了 我還沒來得及解釋呢
The two extra fingers freaked me out a little.
突然多出兩隻手指 嚇得我要死
I figured I'd get your attention.
我只是想引起你的注意
I did the same to Gandhi. He didn't eat for three weeks.
我對甘地也這麼做過... 他為此絕食了三個星期
Anyway, here's the deal.
總之... 聽好了
You have all my powers. Use them any way you choose.
你有我所有的神力 你可以以你選擇的方式任意使用
There are two rules. You can't tell anybody you're God.
只有兩條規則 你不能告訴任何人你是上帝
Believe me, you don't want the attention. And you can't mess with free will.
相信我 你會為之後悔的 而且你不能干涉自主意志
- Can I ask why? - Yes! You can!
- 我可以問為什麼嗎? - 可以!
That's the beauty of it.
這正是它的動人之處!
- This is amazing. - Speaking of amazing, excuse me.
- 這太神奇了 - 說到神奇... 讓讓
Holy sh - ... Cow.
王八... 牛啊!
Since you're through with these, I'll keep them.
既然你不要它 我就先幫你保管
Might come in handy some day.
說不定某天會回到你手上的
See you around, kid.
回見 小子
- Where are you going? - I'm... taking a vacation.
- 你要去哪兒? - 我... 去度假
God doesn't take vacations.
上帝不是不度假的嗎?
Does he? Do... ye?
現在可以? 以前也可以?
Did you ever hear of the Dark Ages?
你聽說過暗之世紀嗎?
I'm covered. You can clear everything up in five minutes if you want.
而且 我有你頂著 如果你高興的話 5分鐘就可以搞定啊
Right?
對不?
And he saw that it was good.
這種感覺就是爽啊
B - E - A - utiful!
潑... 伊... 傲... 漂亮!
Check it out.
看啊! 看啊!
Look, it's the hero.
看 這不是英雄兄嗎
- Whassup, homie? - Yo, brethren, what up with thee?
- 你還好嗎? 諸位兄弟們 - 真是不走運啊
- Blessings on your alley. - Want another can of whup ass?
- 祝福降臨到你們這條巷子裡了 - 你又活得不耐煩了嗎?
- You didn't get enough? - He wants some more!
- 你還沒爽夠嗎 英雄先生? - 他真的沒爽夠!
Surely, I say unto you dudes, I do not wish to fight.
聽好了 小子們 我並不想打架
So as soon as you apologize and make a reckoning of your transgressions,
如果你們立即道歉 並且從此改邪歸正
I shall absolve you and continue along the path of righteousness.
我就寬恕你們 大家各走各的路
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼啊?
You talk kind of funny.
你真的很有意思 不過我也真的不知道
I don't know if you lost it up here or what.
你的腦袋裡是不是少了點什麼?
You want me and the homies to apologize? Cool.
你要我們道歉是嗎? 沒問題
We'll apologize the day a monkey comes out of my butt. How about that?
哪天我屁股裡要是鑽出只猴子來 我們就向你道歉 好嗎?
What a coincidence! Because that's today.
實在是太巧了! 因為那就是... 今天!
Did that monkey just come out your crack?
剛剛是不是有只猴子從你屁眼裡鑽出來?
This is some voodoo shit!
- 巫術! - 魔鬼啊! 逃命啊!
You guys leaving?
怎麼就走啦?
Don't forget your parting gifts!
我還有禮物要送給你們哦
Hey, little anal - dwelling butt monkey.
屁股裡蹦出來的的小猴子
Time for you to go home.
你該回去了 小朋友
I am Bruce Almighty.
我就是全能的布魯斯!
My will be done!
心想事成!
What if God was one of us
如果上帝就在我們之中
Just a slob like one of us
只是我們之中的一條懶漢
Just a stranger on a bus
只是公車上的一個陌生人
Trying to make his way
正在歸家...
Home
歸家的路上
- My God. - Call me Bruce.
- 上帝啊 - 你可以稱呼我為布魯斯
What happened to you? You seem so...
你怎麼了 這麼這麼...
happy.
... 開心?
Why shouldn't I be? On a night like this.
我有什麼理由不開心呢? 在這樣的夜晚裡...
Those are amazing. What are these?
好漂亮! 這是什麼花?
A new breed. A cross - pollination between tulips and daisies.
這是新品種 由鬱金香和雛菊雜交而成
I call them todayzees.
我稱之為郁金菊
OK.
好吧
Honey, these flowers are beautiful.
親愛的 這些花真是太漂亮了
- But last night... - Last night, I was only human.
- 昨晚... - 昨晚我還是個凡夫俗子
Barry, help me out.
貝裡 幫幫忙
Honey? Hi.
嗨 親愛的
- I've never seen the moon that big. - Yeah.
- 我從沒見過這麼大的月亮! - 是啊
We really shouldn't waste it.
我們可不能虛度了這迷人的月夜
Bedroom?
在臥室做?
Five minutes.
等我五分鐘!
Let there be light.
燭光!
I'll be out in a minute!
還有一分鐘!
Don't rush.
別急...
Sometimes anticipation can heighten the...
有時候慢慢來反而會更有...
pleasure!
快感!
Oh, God.
哦 上帝啊
It's a funny thing about pleasure.
快感難以言表...
It can be quite... pleasurable!
它可以變成... 超快感!
Oh, my God.
噢 上帝啊
Pleasuring, pleasurable.
快感快感 快感快感...
Oh, good God!
快感快感...
In international news:
現在報告國際新聞
Japanese relief workers are staging an effort to rescue hundreds of people
日本救護人員正在搶救
stranded by a freak tidal wave that hit Kitamoto City.
被北本市的奇怪潮汐擱淺的數百名遊客...
Scientists say the tsunami may have been caused
科學家說這種現象可能是
by what they are describing as unusual lunar activity.
由他們所說的"反常的月球運動"造成的...
More on this as it develops.
"進一步情況有待瞭解"
Please bless my mommy, my daddy, and especially my little sister.
"請保佑我的媽媽 爸爸 還有我的妹妹... "
Please help me, Lord. Please get me through this one.
"請幫幫我 主啊 請幫我度過這難關... "
Thank you for everything else in my life. Amen.
"感謝您賜予我生命中的這一切 阿門"
Good boy.
好孩子
Forget something?
忘了什麼嗎?
Good boy! There are girls in the house.
乖狗... 家裡有女生的哦
- Morning. - Good morning.
- 早 - 早上好
- I made you grilled cheese. - My favi.
- 我給你做了芝士三文治 - 噢 我的最愛!
- Honey, last night was... - Heavenly. I know.
- 昨晚我... - 像上天堂? 我知道 我知道
I mean, I woke up and I felt like my boobs were bigger.
我是說... 今天早上我一覺醒來 發現... 好像... 我的咪咪變大了
- Do they look bigger to you? - What?
- 你覺得呢? 是不是大了? - 什麼?
No.
噢...
- Bigger? - Oh, come on!
- 變大了嗎? 沒有吧... - 拜託! 看看它們啊!
Look at them.
看嘛...
Please. They are definitely bigger.
絕對是變大了
I mean, look. They feel huge to me.
簡直是碩大無比 對我而言
I have to go.
瞧 我得出門了
But this has been the breast bek...
這早餐真好...
Thank you.
謝謝
- Where are you going? - To get my job back.
- 你要去哪兒? - 去把我的工作搶回來
Yeah, yeah, I am great
我真行 我真好
Good grief! Is that what I'm driving?
好啊! 這就是我的車?
Nice car, man.
好漂亮的車! 夥計!
Yeah, it gets me from A to B.
是的 這才能襯托我的身份
Darn. All this horsepower and no room to gallop!
天呀 這兒有這麼多車 沒有路來飛馳?
Hi - yo, Silver. Away!
銀駒! 沖啊!
I wouldn't want to be a fugitive
我肯定不想成為被漢克追捕的逃犯
with Hank, Buffalo's number one police dog, on the job.
水牛鎮警方的首席警犬正在演習
Phil Sidleman at the police canine training center,
這是菲莉·西蒙 正在員警的訓練中心為你報導
Channel 5 News.
這是第五頻道新聞節目
And cut it.
可以停了
Look what the cat coughed up!
瞧瞧這是誰呀
Channel 7, right? You're the guy that went crazy.
是第7頻道的 對嗎? 是那個發瘋的傢伙
- I had a bad moment. - What are you doing here?
- 我那段時間很揹運 - 你來這裡幹什麼?
- Looking for a story. - No story here.
- 來找新聞 - 這裡沒有新聞
This pond is all fished out. Pretty standard stuff, anyway.
這池塘的魚都釣完了 一流的素材
My instinct tells me there's something more.
我不知道 我的直覺告訴我還有事發生
Well, go with that. It served you well in the past, right?
那就繼續堅持吧 以前你的直覺也不錯吧?
Hank found something!
嘿 漢克發現了些東西
We got a body!
我們找到了具屍體!
Shit. Get the camera! Now!
去拿攝像機! 立刻!
- It's locked! The keys are inside! - I guess every dog has his day.
- 鎖住了! 鑰匙在裡面! - 我想這就是風水輪流轉
- Kid, you want to make $10? - Sure.
- 小子 想賺10塊錢嗎? - 當然
- Know how to use one of these? - Duh.
- 你會用這個吧? - 不會
Seems to be in tune. Let's do this.
看來沒有走調 我們來吧
The body of Jimmy Hoffa was uncovered in a field today
吉米·霍夫曼的屍體今天在紐約市水牛鎮
outside a canine training center in Buffalo, New York.
附近的訓練中心的一處草坪被發現
- Bruce Nolan was first on the scene. - Thank you, Jane.
- 布魯斯·諾蘭是第一個趕到現場的人 - 謝謝 簡
As you can see, the body is being carefully exhumed
大家可以見到就在我身後 該屍體正被仔細地挖掘出來
for transportation to a facility where DNA can confirm the identity.
然後會被送到法醫處進行DNA鑒定 以確定身份
That, however, merely a formality at this point,
不過 這一切只不過是手續而已
as the body was found with
因為在屍體旁奇跡般的發現了
a birth certificate and dental records.
與案件相關的檔和死者的牙醫記錄
I'd call that a red - letter day for any canine unit.
我想今天是適宜掘屍的吉日
But was that enough for Hank? No, siree.
不過這對漢克來說還不算什麼
Moments later, he busted a local news camera crew
因為發現屍體之後不久 它還發現一輛本地媒體的採訪車上
with 220 pounds of marijuana.
裝有100公斤的大麻
I never saw it before! I swear!
我沒有見過這東西! 我發誓!
I'm Bruce Nolan...
這裡是布魯斯·諾蘭
and that's the way the cookie crumbles.
曲奇... 是這樣吃的
Did you like that?
你覺得怎麼樣?
Thank you, thank you.
謝謝 謝謝!
- Hi, Bruce. - Hi, Susan.
- 嗨 布魯斯 - 嗨 蘇姍
Good work. I'm impressed.
幹得好 你令我刮目相看
- Did you need me for something? - Bruce!
- 傑克 要我做點什麼事嗎? - 布魯斯 布魯斯!
Just the man I want to see.
我正要找你
- Hoffa? What are the odds of that? - What are the odds of that?
- 霍夫曼... 那事的反應如何? - 什麼是... 什麼反應如何...
- Bruce, why don't you sit down? - OK.
- 布魯斯 請坐 - 好的
I'm going to be straight with you. We want you back, Bruce.
我打算開門見山地和你談談 我們想要你回來 布魯斯
But I want you to understand it was not my decision to let you go.
但我想要你明白的是 炒你魷魚的決定不是我做的
- When the big guy gives the order... - No harm, no foul.
- 是幕後的大人物下的命令 你知道的... - 不用擁抱 不用道歉
I needed to reassess my goals and get in touch with my true self.
我需要時間重新設定我真正想做的事
- You did that in a day? - Imagine what I could do with seven.
- 給你一天節目時間 如何? - 我想我有能力做7天的
It is not in my power to give you anchor.
你知道的 布魯斯 我沒有權力給你主持人的職位
As far as field reporting goes, if you're looking for a bump...
只需要繼續有新聞 如果你想得到升遷
Let's cut the crap and get down to brass tacks.
傑克 我們廢話少說 我們開誠佈公吧
I had you going.
你 看你的樣子
Don't worry about it, my old friend.
別擔心 老朋友
Just give me a camera. I'll give you the news.
只要你給我攝像機 傑克 我會給你新聞的
My secret is that I let the jalapenos marinate in a spicy sauce
我的秘訣是就在於可以把特殊的味道融入到
for at least 24 hours before I stir it into the chilli.
一種非常美味的菜汁中 然後等24小時後 我才開始製作
Then I let it all come to a simmer.
我將所有的東西都放在一個鍋裡...
Hold that thought. It seems as if an asteroid or meteorite
留在這裡 夫人 你們看到了嗎? 一個小行星 或是某種隕星
has just hit ground right outside the Mark Twain Chilli Cook - Off!
剛剛墜落地面 就在... 馬克吐溫市場美食節現場外面
This should certainly spice things up a bit!
這將是你見過得最熱辣的東西
His stories are all over town.
這是全城的歷史時刻
From unearthing Hoffa
自從發現了吉米·霍夫曼
..to a meteor crashing,
到流星的墜落
..Bruce Nolan is rapidly becoming known as...
布魯斯·諾蘭 已經成為了 獨家新聞先生
And that's the way the cookie crumbles!
水牛鎮曲奇就是這樣製成的!
This was Bruce's idea?
這是布魯斯的主意嗎?
He wanted me to have a day of beauty and luxurious serenity.
他說要我做一整天的美容 豪華而舒適
I got to tell you, he is impressing me lately.
我要告訴你 最近他令我刮目相看
Know where he's taking me to dinner?
你知道他今天要帶我去哪裡共進晚餐?
Where?
去哪裡?
The Blue Palm?
藍棕櫚飯店?
- My gosh, I got chills. - I know.
- 啊我的天 他抓住你 - 我知道...
He told me to prepare for the most memorable night of our lives.
他說 為你一生都會記住的一晚 做好準備
Oh, my gosh. He's going to propose.
我的老天 格雷斯 他想求婚了
Oh, stop it. No. He's...
別說了...
- Really? - Yeah, really.
- 真的? - 是的 別這樣
Do the math. He sends you all day to a beauty spa,
你想想 他讓你來美容院一整天
he's taking you to a restaurant where you had your first date. Hello!
你們去那間本城最浪漫的飯店 你們第一次見面就在那裡
I never thought I'd say this, but Bruce is right.
我認為將這個說成一次求婚是不正確的
This is your night. Relax and enjoy it.
這是重要的一晚上 讓我們好好享受!
Oh, God.
老天呀
Welcome to Eyewitness News at Six, with Susan Ortega,
歡迎收看6點鐘新聞 主持人包括蘇珊·奧爾特加
Evan Baxter,
埃文·巴克斯特
Fred Donohue, sports, Dallas Coleman, weather.
佛瑞德... 體育節目 達拉斯·科爾曼... 時事
And now, Buffalo's number one news team.
現在 這裡是水牛鎮第一新聞報導組
Welcome to Eyewitness News at Six.
晚安 歡迎收看6點鐘新聞
- I'm Susan Ortega. - I'm Evan Baxter.
- 我是蘇珊.奧爾特加 - 我是埃文·巴克斯特
Here's what's making news.
今天的新聞是
A potential scandal with the Buffalo PD surfaced today,
令人懷疑的水牛鎮警方醜聞
when the mayor demanded that...
當市長...
When the mayor demanded the chief of...
Issued a response to...
對不起
I seem to have something stuck in my...
有東西噎住了了
Get him some water.
給他點水喝
Looks like my new co - anchor may need water.
看起來 我的搭檔需要杯水
There we go. Sorry.
好了 對剛才的事很抱歉
In other news, the prime minister of Sweden visited Washington today,
另一條新聞是 瑞典首相今天訪問華盛頓
and my tiny little nipples went to France.
還有我的小情人去了法國
What did he say? Check the prompter.
他在胡說什麼? 檢查下電子提示器
- The prompter's fine. - Evan, read the copy.
- 提示器是好的 - 埃文 請跟著文本讀
The copy's good. Just read it.
文本沒有問題 照著讀
The White House committee greeted the prime rib roast minister,
白宮會議通過了首相的提議
and I do the cha - cha like a sissy girl.
還有我像個女人般地跳喳喳舞
I lika do...
我喜歡... 跳...
da cha - cha.
喳喳舞
I'm sorry. We seem to be having technical difficulties.
抱歉 看起來我們好像有點技術問題
In other news...
另一條新聞是
My apologies.
對不起
- May I? - Certainly.
- 可以嗎? - 當然
It's perfect. She'll love it.
太完美了 她應該會喜歡的
You know, I was going to wait until after the meal,
你知道嗎? 我將... 我終於揚眉吐氣了
but it'll burst out of me like an alien if I don't do it now.
他們再也不能把我當白癡了 我不會讓他們這麼做的了
Oh, my God. OK.
老天 沒事的
This is it, isn't it?
會發生什麼事?
I don't know if I'm ready for this.
我不知道 我還沒準備好
I mean, I'm ready. I just didn't know if I would... I'm sorry, go on.
我不是說我還沒準備好 我只是有點緊張 對不起 繼續說
- I didn't know it was so important to you. - Me neither.
- 我不知道這對你會有多重要 - 我也不知道
- Grace? - Yes?
- 格雷斯 - 好的
I got anchor.
我成為主持人了
No.
噢...
Yes. Apparently it wasn't working out with Evan,
是的 他們要辭掉埃文
so he's going to finish out the week and I go live on Monday.
這周他就要走人 星期一我就要上任了
- That's great, honey. - I know, I know.
- 太好了 親愛的 - 我知道
Well...
那麼...
- So that's what this is all about. - Well, yeah.
- 就是為了這些事情嗎? - 是的
We got anchor.
格雷斯 我是主持人了
Jack's throwing me a party at the Vanderbilt estate to celebrate.
傑克星期五要凱歌晚會為我慶祝
- What's the matter? - Nothing.
- 怎麼了? - 沒事
Now I lay me down to sleep...
我現在只想躺下睡覺
I feel stupid.
啊 我多笨呀
- It is loud in here, isn't it? - No, it's not loud.
- 啊 這裡太吵了 不是嗎? - 不 這裡不吵
Jeez! Can you keep it down to a dull roar?
你們能小聲點嗎?
- Thank you! - Is that supposed to be funny?
- 謝謝! - 這很搞笑嗎?
Cos that is not funny.
這一點都不搞笑
- What did you say? - What is wrong with you? Stop yelling.
- 你在說什麼? - 你怎麼了? 不要叫嚷
If you'll excuse me, I'll take a little trip to the...
對不起 我要出去...
The wine is going right through me.
那酒的作用 我有點醉了
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
對不起 真得很抱歉
- Keep going, Tony! - Oh, God.
- 繼續 托尼! 你很棒! - 噢 上帝!
What is going on here?
怎麼了?
What is this?
這是怎麼回事?
Give me a break!
別來煩我!
Really something, isn't it?
非常吵雜 是不是?
Is this heaven?
這裡是天堂嗎?
No, this is Mount Everest.
不是 這是珠穆朗瑪峰
Flip on the Discovery Channel from time to time.
你應該經常在探索頻道看到過
But I guess you can't now, being dead and all.
但我想你現在無法看到了 你已經死了
- I'm dead? - I'm just messing with you.
- 我死了嗎? - 沒有 只想忽悠你一下
That's not funny, man!
那並不好笑 夥計!
What about the voices in my head? Is that part of the hilarity?
我腦子裡的聲音是怎麼回事? 這也是笑話的一部分?
No, those are prayers. You keep ignoring them,
那些是禱告的人 你不斷地忽視他們
they're going to build up.
他們就集聚在你的頭腦中
But it's just noise. I can't understand them.
那些只是些噪音 我無法弄明白的噪音
You're not listening, son.
是你沒有留心聽 孩子
Let's see.
我們來看看吧
You had my powers for a little over a week. How many people have you helped?
你擁有我能力的有一周了 你已幫助了多少人?
I took care of a few things.
我 我照管你的事情
I righted a few wrongs in my own life first. OK?
無論這是對失錯 我得先管好自己的事 這排第一 行吧?
I was going to help the others.
然後我才會去幫助別人
- I think I could help the world. - The world?
- 我想我有能力幫助全世界 - 全世界?
That wasn't the world. That was just Buffalo, between 57th and Commonwealth.
不用管全世界 只是水牛鎮 在57條街道之間的眾生
I didn't want to start you off with more than you could handle.
我只能給你 你的能力所及的工作給你
You took the job, Bruce, so I suggest you get to it.
既然你領了工作 我建議你開始工作吧
Seeing him smile would make me so happy.
看到他的微笑會讓我高興萬分
Prayers, prayers, OK.
禱告者們 禱告者們 好的 禱告者們
This creepy whisper thing has to end.
這些聲音令我難受!
Organization. That's what I need.
我需要的是有組織的 可以方便管理
I need a system. Something concrete. Concentrate.
一個系統 有點實體化 集中精神
Files. Let all prayers be organized into files.
檔形式 把所有的禱告組織成檔形式
That takes care of the voices. Not exactly a space - saver, though.
我到哪裡去照看那些聲音呢 還有這占了太多的空間
Grace might notice.
格雷斯會發覺的
I know. Prayer Post - its!
我知道了 用便簽!
OK, I need something with a lock. Security. Combination. A password.
我需要能具有鎖上的 有安全保障 還有密碼功能
A password.
密碼!
Welcome to the revelation superhighway.
歡迎參觀革命性的禱告方式
We bless, no mess. Downloading now.
我們保證不會有遺漏 下載... 開始
It's good.
不錯 不錯
This is going to take a while.
這要花點時間
1,527,503 prayer requests?
1527503個禱告請求?
I better manifest some coffee.
我能喝點咖啡嗎?
Now that's fresh, mountain - grown coffee from the hills of Colombia.
這是來之哥倫比亞山區的新鮮咖啡!
Good.
味道真不錯
OK, I had to have made some kind of a dent by now.
好的 我終於做完了
Oh, come on!
啊 別這樣!
What a bunch of whiners. This is going to suck up my whole life.
你們這些作者怎麼了? 這樣會用掉我一生的
You know what?
你懂什麼?
Yes. To all.
同意! 給所有人!
Yeah. There you go. Now everybody's happy.
是的 我們搞掂了 現在大家都開心了
I'll drink to that. My tech stocks tripled in five days.
我告訴過你嗎? 我的股票5天漲了3倍
Know something, Joe? You seem taller.
你知道嗎 喬? 你看上去長高了
- I am. - My daughter pitched a no - hitter.
- 我確實是 - 我女兒不做擊球員了
I lost 47 pounds on the Krispy Kreme diet.
我只吃餅乾就減了47磅
There he is!
嗨 他來了
The man of the hour!
今天的主角
Bless you! Bless all of you!
保佑你們 保佑你們所有人
Be fruitful and... do long division or something!
有成就 在某些事上表現的不平凡
Try that. It's an excellent year.
品嘗下 今年真是非凡的一年
Bruce! Who do you like in the game tonight?
嗨 布魯斯! 你喜歡今天的遊戲嗎?
I like the Sabres. Coach prays a lot.
我希望賽布勒斯能贏!
This is Bruce, Grace and Sam. Leave a message.
這是布魯斯 格雷斯和薩姆 請留下口信
Grace? Are you there?
格雷斯? 你在嗎?
Hello? It's me.
在嗎? 是我
Come on, Grace. Come to the party.
別這樣 格雷斯 來參加晚會
I'll call you later, OK?
我待會再給你電話 好嗎?
Come on, Sam.
快點 薩姆
Help me out here.
幫下我
Sam, don't. Come on.
薩姆 別這樣!
- Tell me. - If I do, it might not come true.
- 告訴我 - 你想要什麼?
What is it you want, Mary? You want the moon?
你想要什麼 瑪麗? 你想要月亮嗎?
Say the word and I'll throw a lasso around it and pull it down.
說呀 我會把它扯下來的
H.ey, that's a pretty good idea. I'll give you the moon, Mary.
這是個好主意 我給你月亮 好嗎?
I'll take it.
我會拿到的
- Then what? - Then you could swallow it.
- 然後呢? - 然後你就可以吃了它
And it'd all dissolve.
最後就沒了 明白?
Moonbeams would shoot out of your fingers and toes
然後月光就會從你的手指 你的腳趾射出來
and the ends of your hair.
還有從你的頭髮上出來
This is Bruce, Grace and Sam.
這是布魯斯 格雷斯和薩姆...
Hi, Bruce.
你好 布魯斯
What are you doing in here all alone?
你一個人在這裡做什麼?
Oh, I was just going to...
我只是...
I mean...
我是說...
I was going to give Grace a call.
我只是... 等格雷斯的電話
Yeah, I didn't see her. So how are you and Grace doing?
是的 在那邊我沒有見到她 你和格雷斯相處得如何?
Well, actually, we had a bit of a fight.
實際上 我和她剛剛有個爭執
Kind of. I'm not sure if she's...
某種... 過火
You're on fire, Bruce.
想要有點激情嘛 布魯斯?
Some women can't handle fire.
這裡的某個女人可以幫你來點激情
Some can.
那麼一點點
That's interesting, cos I never thought we would ever talk...
這真有趣 因為我認為我們從來沒有交談...
You might want to stop touching me now.
你現在可不可以不碰我
Grace, come here!
格雷斯 過來
This is weird. I was just calling you.
這太怪了 我當時正在給你電話...
And you thought Susan's mouth was the phone?
啊 你以為蘇珊的嘴是電話嗎?
She kissed me. I'm the kissee.
是她吻我 我是被吻的
You were putting up a big fight.
啊 我看到你極力抗拒了
I tried to stop her, but she's really strong.
我想阻止她 她太強壯了
OK, I screwed up. Can I make it up to you?
好了! 我被人算計了 你要我給你什麼補償?
Yeah. Why don't you get me a boat?
啊是了... 你給我一艘船吧 布魯斯?
- What? - A big boat.
- 什麼? - 是的 一艘大船
And maybe two big bags of cash.
或者兩大箱現金
Then, then, I'll be happy.
那我就會開心了
Lots of money and lots of stuff!
許多的錢和許多的東西
People want crap like getting married or having babies with the man they love.
其他人有那種白癡的想法 想和她相愛5年的生孩子
But not me, Bruce. Just give me the boat.
但我不是 布魯斯! 給我那船
No wonder you stayed single!
你為什麼還不想結婚!
- Don't do this. - I'm not doing this. I'm undoing it.
- 格雷斯 別這樣! - 我沒有那樣做 我什麼也沒做
I'll be at Debbie's. Take care of Sam until I make arrangements.
我要去黛比那裡 像我平時那樣 照顧薩姆
You can't leave me.
你不能離開我
I'm the Alpha, lady!
我是第一 寶貝
I'm the Omega, baby!
我是造物者 寶貝!
Fine! I don't need you!
好吧 沒事! 我不需要你
What's the matter, Bruce? She can't handle a little competition?
怎麼啦 布魯斯? 她無法應付一點點競爭嗎?
Game's been called on account of rain.
晚會由於下雨而取消
An unusually high number of lottery winners has officials concerned.
不同尋常多的彩票中獎人數 令組織者關注
So far, 1, 100 winning tickets have been turned in,
超過一萬一千人中獎
all, strangely, from the Buffalo area.
非常奇怪的是 都在水牛鎮地區
More on this story as it develops.
隨著情況的發展 會有進一步的報導
Enjoying your party?
喜歡這個晚會嗎?
Nothing like spending quality time with great friends.
沒有什麼比和高貴的朋友共度時光更好的了
- Grace left me. - Yeah, I know.
- 格雷斯離開我了 - 我知道
She'll take me back.
她會要我回去的
- She'll take me back, right? - Would you take you back?
- 她會要我回去的 對嗎? - 你想要她回來嗎?
How do you make somebody love you without affecting free will?
你如何才能讓別人愛你 卻不用影響別人的選擇?
Welcome to my world, son.
歡迎來到我的世界 孩子
You come up with an answer to that one, you let me know.
如果你對在這種事上找到了答案 請告訴我
Rise and shine, Buffalo.
水牛鎮陽光明媚的一天
It's 70 and sunny and the perfect day to forgive Bruce.
是原諒布魯斯的最完美的日子
- Bye. - Have fun.
- 再見 - 玩的愉快
- Hi. Can I get a small coffee to go? - Sure, hon. Just a sec.
- 你好 能給我一小杯咖啡嗎? - 好的 寶貝 等一會
K - Tel Records brings you the 100 greatest love songs of all time.
K - TEL唱片公司奉獻古今100首情歌
You'll hear such classics as "All You Need Is Bruce",
你想聽這些經典情歌 只需要布魯斯
"If You Can't Be With The One You Love, Then Love Bruce",
如果你還沒找到你的所愛 那麼就愛布魯斯吧
"Do That To Bruce One More Time".
和布魯斯再來一次
Who can forget that classic,
而誰又能忘記這些經典之作呢?
"Bruce So H.orny H.e Love You Long Time"?
布魯斯很性感! 他一直愛著你
Order today and we'll throw in at no extra charge
今天就訂購 附送沒有額外的費用的
the video "Sweatin' To Bruce".
和布魯斯一起瘋狂
Just dial 1-900-FORGIVE H.IM.
只要撥打 1900原諒他
That's 1-900-FORGIVE H.IM. Do it now.
就是1900原諒他 現在就行動
No, no! Please don't put that in your mouth.
不 不 不要把那放進嘴裡
That's not food.
不要吃那東西
Go to the bathroom. Wash out your mouth. Wash off your hands.
啊 這不好 去洗手間 清洗下你得嘴和雙手
That kid is gonna poop an ornament.
上帝呀 什麼都敢吃
One more time, you're going to be in a lot of trouble.
再來一次的話 你就會有大麻煩!
All right, that's it!
好了! 這就是 這就是
I surrender!
我投降 我投降!
Hi.
嗨!
I'm... doing my first anchor tonight.
我將... 今晚將第一次做主持人
Oh, wow. That's great!
哇! 太好了!
- How have you been doing? - Good.
- 你怎麼想? - 很好
- Debbie won the lottery. - Oh, yeah? You're kidding.
- 啊 黛比中了彩票 - 啊 是嗎?
But so did 400, 000 other people,
他和40萬人一起中了獎
so she only won like $17 or something.
所以她只得到17元
I miss you.
我想念你
I took a first step.
好的 我主動點
Jumped out on a ledge.
先勾畫出框框
- Feeling vulnerable. - What do you want me to say?
- 你也相當悶 - 我不知道你想我說什麼
Say you want me back.
說你愛我 你想要我回來
What about all the signs?
不 布魯斯 那些天邊的啟示表示什麼?
How did you know about that? Did you talk to Debbie?
你怎麼知道那事的? 你同黛比談過了?
Would it help if I just said I was a complete ass?
你願意幫忙告訴我 我是個大混...
- You said ass! - It's OK if I'm talking about a donkey.
- 嘿 你說粗話 - 沒事的
I didn't say "hole". If I said ass...
我沒有說"蛋"字... 我說"混"...
No, wait. OK, honey, let's go inside.
孩子們 我們走! 去裡面!
All right, everybody inside. Time to go inside.
孩子們 大家都進去 該進去了!
Please. None of this seems right without you.
格雷斯 求你了 沒了你一切都不對頭
I gotta go.
我得走了
Wait!
等等!
How do you feel now?
你現在感覺任何?
Have you completely lost your mind?
你真得徹底... 瘋了?
- Are you drunk? - Yeah. Drunk with power.
- 還是喝醉了? - 我喝醉了 徹底醉了!
Love me.
愛我!
I did.
我愛過
Yeah, I know. Free will.
好了 我知道了 自由的思想
More power outages reported today caused by last week's meteorite strike.
越來越多的停電的報告 因為上次隕星的墜落
Officials are trying to repair transformers
有關方面疲於修復
damaged by the ensuing electrical surge.
隕星爆炸破壞的變壓器
The scene nearly turned violent
現場變得失控
when Buffalo residents protested last week's lottery results.
當數百名水牛鎮居民 抗議上周的彩票結果
Doomsayers are pointing to last week's strange celestial events
末日的恐懼和上周的奇怪的事情被人們視為
as signs that prophecy is being fulfilled and the world may be coming to an end.
預言就要實現的徵兆 現在的世界將終結
The world's gone mad.
瘋了
- 30 seconds to air. - OK.
- 布魯斯 30秒鐘 - 好的
There you are. It's your debut. How are you feeling?
到你了 你的大日子 感覺如何?
You know what? I'm fine. Never better.
很好 從來沒有這麼好過
The show must go on right?
我們開始了 是嗎?
- The Sabres just won the Stanley Cup. - You're kidding me!
- 剃刀隊剛剛贏史丹尼員警隊 - 你開玩笑嗎?
Was that tonight? That's great.
是今晚嗎? 太好了 不是嗎?
It's crazy out there. We're going to kick live to Fred at the stadium, OK?
我們得直播在體育館的佛瑞德的情況 好嗎?
- Five seconds to the open. - This is it.
還有5秒鐘開播
- You ready? - Born that way.
- 開始? 準備好了嗎? - 一直準備好的!
Welcome to Eyewitness News at Six, with Susan Ortega, Bruce Nolan,
歡迎收看6點鐘新聞 由蘇珊·奧爾特加 布魯斯·諾蘭
Fred Donohue, sports, Dallas Coleman, weather.
佛瑞德... 體育 達拉斯·科爾曼... 天氣
Now Buffalo's number one news team.
這裡是水牛鎮第一的新聞報導小組
- I'm Susan Ortega. - I'm Bruce Nolan.
- 我是蘇珊·奧爾特加 - 我是布魯斯·諾蘭
And here's what's making news.
今天的新聞是
- What happened? - We lost power.
- 什麼事? - 停電了
- Transformer's down again. - Jeez.
- 變壓器壞了 - 老天
Ever since that damn meteorite hit.
都是那該死的隕星
- We're back. - We apologize for the interruption.
- 好了 有電了 - 我們為剛才的中斷抱歉
- Back to the news. Bruce? - Thank you.
- 現在開始報導新聞 布魯斯 - 謝謝 蘇珊
I'm sorry. We're going live to HSBC Arena,
對不起 我們現在要直播水牛鎮剃刀隊
where the Buffalo Sabres have won the Stanley Cup.
所在的體育館的情況 他們剛剛贏了史丹尼員警隊
- Great. - Fred?
- 太好了 - 佛瑞德
We're about to uncork some champagne because
我們準備開香檳 因為剃刀隊在這裡贏得了
the Sabres have won their first championship in 22 years!
22年來的第一個冠軍...
What in blazes...
正中頭部
We'll be back with the Sabres' victory in just a hot second.
我們一會再回到現場報導 很快
In other news...
另一條新聞是
- Bloody hell! - What is it now?
- 又來了? 怎麼回事? - 不 不是的
- The whole booth is down. - It's not!
保險全壞了
In other news, fighting erupted in the Gaza Strip today,
另一條新聞 衝突今天在加沙又起
as Israelis and Palestinians...
巴勒斯坦人...
- Bruce. - What?
- 布魯斯 - 什麼?
We've got a situation here. They're rioting right outside.
本地有狀況 暴亂失控了
- You're kidding. - The whole town has gone crazy.
- 別和我開玩笑了 - 全城都瘋了!
Go on, Bruce. Say something.
布魯斯 說話呀
Ladies and gentlemen, this just in.
女士們先生們 報導結束了
Possibly the biggest breaking news story this town has ever seen.
本城發生了也許是你從未見過的突發事件
And I gotta go.
我得走了
Sorry, Jack.
對不起 傑克
Susan, it's all yours.
蘇珊 我對不起大家
Sabres!
剃刀!
Sabres rule!
剃刀隊是第一!
Down with the lottery!
終止博彩!
Repent! The end is near!
懺悔吧! 末日來了
The lottery sucks!
博彩是騙局!
I only won 17 bucks!
只有17元
Channel 7 lies!
第7頻道是騙子!
Oh, no!
不!
God!
上帝呀!
God?
上帝?
Are you here?
你在嗎?
Hello? I need your help!
你好! 我需要幫助!
Clap on!
鼓掌 鼓掌
Figures!
快點出現吧
Well, hello there, Bruce Almighty.
我就知道! 那邊的 你好 全能的布魯斯
Not as easy as it looks, is it, son? This God business.
看起來很容易 不是嗎 孩子? 上帝的工作
They're all out of control.
一切都失控了!
It's me. I don't know what to do.
他們瘋了 我束手無策
Well, you're right on time. Seven o'clock.
你來得很準時 7點鐘
The 7th at 7.00.
7點 到7點
All righty, then.
啊 做完了
- There we are. - It's good.
- 就到這裡 - 不錯 不錯
It's a wonderful thing.
了不起的事情
No matter how filthy something gets, you can always clean it right up.
無論搞得多亂 我們總能清理好
There were so many. I just gave them all what they wanted.
他們有太多的要求了 我只能滿足他們的需要
Yeah.
是啊
But since when does anyone have a clue about what they want?
那麼是你在什麼時候有了線索... 什麼是他們所需要的呢?
So what do I do?
那麼我該怎麼做?
Parting your soup is not a miracle.
分開一盆濃湯並不是什麼奇跡
It's a magic trick.
那只是一個小小的魔術把戲而已
A single mom who's working two jobs
一位單身媽媽 每天要打兩份工
and still finds time to take her kid to soccer practice, that's a miracle.
但還是能抽的出時間陪孩子參加足球練習 那才是一種奇跡
A teenager who says no to drugs and yes to an education,
年輕人說要遠離毒品 而且要努力受教育
that's a miracle.
這也是一種奇跡
People want me to do everything for them.
人們要求我為他們實現任何他們自己的願望
What they don't realize is they have the power.
但是他們從來沒有意識到 他們自己具有實現自己願望的能力
You want to see a miracle, son?
年輕人 想要看到真正的奇跡
Be the miracle.
首先得要自己努力
Wait. Are you leaving?
等一下 你要走了嘛?
Yeah. I figure you can handle things now.
是啊! 我想你現在可以自己解決問題了
But what if I need you?
但如果我又需要你説明
What if I have questions?
或者我又有別的問題的時候怎麼辦?
That's your problem, Bruce.
這就是你的問題嘍 布魯斯!
That's everybody's problem.
這也是我們每個人的問題
You keep looking up.
你要繼續留神嘍
Order has been restored after this evening's downtown riot.
在今天的示威遊行之後 水牛鎮本地的秩序已經恢復正常
State officials have suspended all lottery sales
官方已經終止了博彩的銷售
pending further investigation.
正在尋找妥善的解決方法
No injuries were reported in the melee, however there were dozens of arrests.
這次示威遊行中沒有傷亡報告
OK.
好
- Thanks a million. - Not a problem.
- 萬分感謝 - 小意思
God bless.
上帝保佑你
Bruce giveth and Bruce... taketh away.
布魯斯給予你們的 布魯斯再次收回
If you don't like it... mega - bite me.
你們要是不情願的話 來咬我吧
- Evan? - Bruce.
- 埃文 - 布魯斯
I suppose you're here to gloat about
我想你是回來取代我的主持人身份的吧
the anchor position. Go ahead.
它們是你的了 作出你最好的報導吧
Well, actually, I...
實際上
I just came to tell you that I've been a royal prick.
我是來告訴你 我放棄了從事主持方面的工作了
The anchor position is yours. I turned down the job.
位置給你留著 我辭掉了這份工作
And I never really congratulated you.
對了! 我還沒有向你的祝賀呢
Congratulations.
恭喜了!
Thanks, Bruce.
多謝了! 布魯斯
In the financial world, things are back to normal
目前的金融界 一切都歸於平常
in what analysts are calling a fluke market fluctuation.
我們稱其為 平衡的市場效應
- You made the right move. - What about you?
- 你這一步走得不錯! - 傑克? - 嗯! 那麼你準備怎麼樣?
You ready to go back out there?
準備繼續回到外面
Do the cutesy stuff? The lighter side of the news?
去捕捉新聞了嘛? 那些可愛的報導
Lower and debase myself for the amusement of strangers?
我必須自降身價去取悅那些我都不認識的人
Yeah, I could do that. Sounds like fun.
嗯! 是啊! 我可以做這些事情 聽上去蠻有趣的
Good.
不錯
OK, Sammy, let's do it right. Like all the other dogs.
好了 薩姆 我們現在就開始了 就像其他所有的狗一樣
I don't want to make you feel bad, but they're laughing at you, pal.
我不想你難受 放鬆 放鬆夥計
Come on. Concentrate.
好! 就這樣 集中你的精神...
Pump it out, if you have to.
快點拉出來吧 如果你必須的話
What am I going to do with you?
天哪! 我要把你怎麼辦?
I know this seems kind of crazy,
我知道這可能看上去很瘋狂
but desperate times call for desperate measures.
但是值得試試 解決你的問題吧
OK, Sammy. Do your thing.
好了 薩姆 你的東西來了!
That's it. Good boy!
就是這樣 就是這樣! 乖孩子!
Training my dog.
正在訓練我的狗
Yes! We did it!
太好了 我們成功了!
We're doing it doggy style
你終於象狗一樣了!
I'll alert Penthouse Forum.
我看你還是老樣子
Hi, Deb. How are you?
你好黛比 還好嘛?
How's Grace?
格雷斯怎麼樣了?
I didn't come to chat.
我不是來聊天的 布魯斯?
I came for Grace's stuff.
我是來拿格雷斯留在你這裡的東西的
- You need a...? - That's OK. I've got it.
- 需要什麼... - 不了 我已經拿完了
I don't know if she...
我... 我不想她把它們賣掉
I don't know if she wants that or not.
我不知道她是否需要
This is full. You did all this?
這裡插滿了啊! 都是你幹的嘛?
You know what I do before I go to bed?
你知道每天晚上我上床前做的事情嘛?
I tuck my kids in, maybe have some ice cream and watch Conan.
我帶著我的孩子 一起看看電影或者電視
Know what Grace does?
想知道格雷斯會做什麼嘛?
She prays.
她會祈禱上帝
Most of the time for you.
大部分時間都是為了你
Find Grace Connelly.
查找關鍵字語"格雷斯·康納利"
The woman does pray a lot.
喔! 女人真是會祈禱
Find... Grace and Bruce.
查找關鍵字語"格雷斯和布魯斯"
"Dear God, please help Bruce find himself,
親愛的上帝 請幫助布魯斯找回他自我吧
find contentment, find you."
讓他學會滿足
"Dear God, please help Bruce.
親愛的上帝啊 請幫幫布魯斯吧!
He seems to be struggling."
他常常為了發現真相而掙扎
"Dear God, give Bruce strength."
親愛的上帝啊 賜予布魯斯力量吧
"Dear God, bless Bruce."
親愛的上帝啊 請保佑布魯斯
It's her.
是她的願望!
Sammy, she's logging on. She's praying right now.
她正登陸上來 正在祈禱
Please, God.
求你了 上帝
Please.
求你了
I still love him.
我還愛著他
But I don't want to love him any more.
但是我不想再繼續愛他下去了
I don't want to hurt any more. Please.
我也不想再受到傷害了! 求你了
Help me forget.
幫我忘記他
Please help me to let it go.
讓我可以忘了他
Please help me let him go.
求你了! 幫我離開他吧
You win!
你贏了!
I'm done!
我完了
Please! I don't want to do this any more!
我不想再幹這個了 求你了
I don't want to be God.
我不想成為上帝了
I want you to decide what's right for me!
我想還是由你來決定我的人生
I surrender to your will!
我向你的意願認輸了
Am I...?
我是不是...
You can't kneel down in the middle of a highway and live to talk about it.
你不可以在高速公路的中間跪了下來 說自己還活著
But why?
為什麼?
Why now?
為什麼現在...?
Bruce...
布魯斯
you have the divine spark.
你擁有神聖的能力
You have the gift for bringing joy and laughter to the world.
你擁有為世界帶來歡樂的天賦
I know. I created you.
放心! 我知道的 是我創造了你嘛
- Quit bragging. - See?
- 你也可以破壞掉它 - 看見了嘛?
That's what I'm talking about.
這就是我對你說的你的能力
That's the spark.
是一種迸發出的火花!
What do you want me to do?
你需要我怎麼做呢?
I want you to pray, son.
孩子! 我要你學會祈禱!
Go ahead. Use them.
繼續下去 記得用到它們
Lord, feed the hungry.
上帝啊! 請你拯救饑荒中的人們
And bring peace to...
還要為全人類
all of mankind.
帶來和平
- How's that? - Great.
- 我說得怎麼樣? - 太好了
If you want to be Miss America.
這是美國小姐的競選詞
Now, come on.
好了! 說吧 你真正關心的東西
What do you really care about?
到底什麼才是你真正喜歡的?
Grace.
格雷斯
You want her back?
你想回到她身邊?
No.
不
I want her to be happy.
我只想她能過得開心
No matter what that means.
不管這意味著什麼
I want her to find someone
我希望她會找到一個
who'll treat her
全身心去愛她的人
with all the love she deserved from me.
那是我所欠她的
I want her to meet someone
我想讓她遇上這樣一個人
who'll see her always
會一直通過她的眼睛
as I do now.
注視著她
Through your eyes.
像現在的我看你一樣
- Now that's a prayer. - Yeah?
- 這就是你的願望嘛? - 是嗎?
Yeah. It's good.
是的 不錯
I'm going to get right on it.
我會幫你辦妥的
Clear!
好了
That didn't feel very good.
這個感覺不是很好!
- Got a rhythm. - I got a pulse.
- 檢查他的脈搏 - 有心跳了!
- Let's get him up. - Get the backboard and brace.
- 讓我們把他抬上擋架 - 固定好靠背和支柱
Welcome back.
布魯斯 歡迎回來
You're lucky to be alive, son.
孩子! 你能活著真是很幸運
Someone up there must like you.
上天一定很眷顧你
I hear all that stuff winds up in a warehouse somewhere.
你還以為這些血被倒掉嗎?
Hi, baby.
寶貝 你還好嗎?
Oh, my God, look at you.
上帝真是保佑了你啊
- I was such an idiot. - It's OK.
- 我真是個笨蛋 - 沒關係! 沒關係的
I don't know what I would have done.
我不知道我應該做些什麼事情
Oh, God. I swear I wanted to be mad at you forever.
我發誓我想和你永遠在一起
Now you're just showing off.
我知道是你顯靈了
This is Bruce Nolan
各位我是 布魯斯·諾蘭
here at Buffalo's first "Be the Miracle" blood drive.
這裡是水牛鎮的第一屆"創造奇跡"獻血動員會
It's a B - E - A - utiful day.
今天是美麗的一天
So come on down, because the life you save could be mine.
所以請來捐血吧 因為可能這次你拯救的就是我呢
Let's go over here. The Kowolskis
過來看看 我們的科洛斯基為了今天的這個場合
have baked a cookie just for this occasion.
他們做了一個十分特殊的餅乾
Sure it's a creepy and a shameless plug, but we love 'em.
看上去可能有點嚇人 還帶有一些血
Thank you, Mama. VOL - finger, nose.
多謝大媽你了 沃爾 注意你的手指
I will have given blood twice this week.
我本人本周接受了2次捐血
For those of you who haven't heard,
為了你們中許多還不知情的人
I'd like to introduce you to the future Mrs Exclusive.
讓我為你們介紹將來的"布魯斯夫人"
Grace Connelly. There she is.
格雷斯·康納利
Look at her! Isn't she beautiful?
大家看看她吧 她漂亮嘛?
She just gave blood and she still has enough left to fill up her face.
她剛剛捐了血 但我看她臉上還有足夠的血色
Yes, behind every great man, there's a woman rolling her eyes, folks.
每個成功男人的背後 都有一個溫柔的女人在支持著他
I'm Bruce Nolan for Eyewitness News reminding you to...
我是"新聞直擊"的布魯斯·諾蘭 和我一起
Be the miracle!
創造奇跡!
You heard 'em.
聽到了嘛?
- OK, cut it. Thank you, Bruce. - Thanks, Ally.
- 好了! 停 多謝了布魯斯 - 多謝 埃莉
- How was that? - Great. That was really great.
- 感覺怎麼樣? - 真是棒極了! 感覺真是很好
Now go over there. The nurse is waiting.
好了 現在在你的後面 護士們在等著你呢
- Do I have to? - Oh, it's not going to hurt.
- 會痛嘛? - 不會的啦
In fact, I think you'll find it pleasurable.
實際上 你會發現這很有快感呢
Baby.
寶貝
Who can take a rainbow, wrap it in a sock
誰能製造一個彩虹 想一口氣就搞定
Soak it in the sun and make a groovy lemon pie?
在太陽裡面浸一下 然後做一個檸檬餡
Oh, Jesus.
噠 噢 天哪
I'm sorry.
對不起
I'm a very rare blood type. I'm AB positive.
我的血型非常特殊 我是AB+
Sounds delicious.
聽起來味道一定很好
Well, there are storehouses all over the world
是的 世界上到處都有倉庫
with tons of stuff on ice, and...
你知道的 所有... 冰上面有非常多的東西
- Sorry. - You were like this. Sorry, go on.
- 這是... 對不起 - 你就像這個 對不起 繼續
Positive, IB positive... Sorry.
陽性 IB+ 對不起
I have a rary...
我有一個"寶貝"...
She has a rary!
她有一個"寶貝"
I have a very rare blood type.
他們需要我的血 我的是稀有血種
I'm AB negative.
我是AB -
- I'm IB positive. - Am I AB negative?
- 我是IB+ - 我是AB-
I don't know what you are any more.
我都不知道你是什麼的了
I'm going to need a frickin' miracle to get to work on time.
我現在需要一個奇跡
That'll work.
應該可以
Other stories in the...
其他新聞在...
The prime minister of Sweden visited Washington today,
今天瑞典首相訪問了華盛頓
and in other...
其他的...
In other...
In other news...
其他的新聞...
I'm Bruce Nolan for Eyewitness No...
我是布露絲·諾蘭 我是證人...
Eyewitness Nose.
見證人諾斯
And clear!
好了 完畢
Be the miracle!
創造奇跡!
That's right!
好極了!